(Penny:)He's smart, he's sweet,
and in the bedroom, whew...
(Penny:)...let me tell you, he really tries.
(Amy:)So it does bother you.
(Penny:)Fine, it bothers me a little.
(Penny:)No, you know what? This is stupid.
It doesn't bother me.
(Penny:)Okay, it bothers me.
(Penny:)But only because she wouldn't stop laughing.
Leonard is not that funny.
(Amy:)And there you have it...
...prefrontal-cortex reasoning
versus limbic lust.
(Amy:)If this were a boxing match
they might call it...
...the Thriller Adjacent to the Amygdala.
(Amy:)If you were a brain scientist,
you would be busting a gut right now.
- So how was work today?
- Oh, it was all right, I guess.
Had to Heimlich a cherry stem
out of Sheldon.
(Leonard:)- Caught Raj right in the eye.
- Oh.